Hello everyone, welcome to this Udemy course. My name is Rahul Tressel and I will be the instructor
for this course. The approach I'm going to take in this course and this particular section,
I'm going to walk you through a real world business problem and then we're going to look at
15 key architectural decisions that you need to make before you start building that production ready
generative AI application. Now this approach will not only help you in passing the exam but also
help you to build the real world generative AI applications and your interviews.
Now let's go and take a look at our business use case scenario. Let's say you are a large
manufacturer who builds wind turbines and you want to build a generic powered equipment subject matter
expert assistant. Large manufacturer wants to build a generative AI powered equipment
SME assistant to reduce wind turbine downtime. Now let's take a look at the scenario.
Let's say there is a wind turbine breakdown in a remote area and we have a field technician
who goes to this remote site. He sends the images of the breakdown and the log incident report.
He sends these details to an custom application which stores the logs and the images and then we have
an equipment SME who's at a global location. He takes a look at these images and incident reports
and then provides guidance to the field technician. Now let's say we want to improve the
equipment of this technician because he has to go through a lot of detailed logs and images.
So the organization decides to build a generic powered equipment SME assistant.
So what the technician does is he sends these images and incident reports to a generative
application built on top of this Amazon bedrock and we'll get into the details of Amazon
bedrock in a bit and for now let's just assume that this generative application sends the summary
of the report back to the technician. So what are the business drivers? So it reduces the wind
turbine downtime and it also helps improve the productivity of the equipment SME. Now in the next
lecture we're going to look at all the 15 architectural decisions that we need to make to build
this kind of a generative application. Okay I'll see the next lecture. Thank you.